Okay, let's make it simpler, the year forty-one,
Хорошо давайте проще сорок первый год
Hitler attacked the Soviet Union Who is
Гитлер напал на Советский Союз Кто
to blame, you know, Hitler had a different
виноват понимаете у Гитлера была иная
goal
цель
Hello Hello, I'm from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsk Where are you
Хмельницке Вы
from? From Moscow, cool listen,
откуда Из Москвы прикольненько слушайте
uh, that's interesting, we saw the news that
ээ вот интересно видели новости что
yesterday, or rather tonight,
вчера точнее сегодня ночью прилетели
Ukrainian drones arrived and hit a
украинские беспилотники ударили в Туле
military oil refinery terminal in Tula
военный Нефтеперерабатывающий терминал
in St. Petersburg in Orel and in
в в санкт-петербурге в Орле и в
Smolensky more goals How are you from Moscow
Смоленский ещё цели Как вы из Москвы
Rate  that Ukrainian drones are already
Оцените что украинские беспилотники уже
striking 800 km deep into
бьют в глубину на 800 км
Russia. It’s sad. But how Putin allows
России Печально А как Путин допускает
this is not specific. Putin allows
это это же не конкретно Путин допускает
this; he doesn’t have subordinates behind this,
такое у не же есть подчин которы за этим
he started his Yes, he understood the consequences, it turns out
он начал сво Да он понимал последствия
he is responsible for
получается он несёт ответственность за
his own, it
сво
turns out I understood And you are here  What are you
получается понял А вы тут О чём
talking about?
общаетесь
Yes, I’m just talking to people,
да я просто с людьми
not just for my own sake. For life, what’s
общаюсь не за сво просто За жизнь что же
going on here that just happens that
проходит
you
те что тебе в жизни
don’t understand how in life, why it should be immediately
непонятно как почему должно сразу быть
incomprehensible to just talk to people
непонятно просто пообщаться с людьми
here  I’m coming in not to discuss just to
сюда захожу не дискутировать просто
talk Let’s talk Let’s talk Let’s
пообщаться Давайте пообщаемся
How are you doing awesome after your
Давайте Как у вас дела офигенно после
arrivals In Russian cities
прилётов По российским городам аж
the mood is already great in the morning
настроение с утра
Sat
классное сат
Sans Well, you just want to talk about the war
Санс Ну вы только за войну хотите
not life force How’s the mood I
говорить не жизни сили Как настроение Я
said No, well, look, you’re weaving a
сказал Не ну ну смотрите Вы опять плета
war again I’m at  you that
ете войну я у вас что другого в жизни
there is nothing else in life except for the fact that now for
ничего нет кроме того что сейчас у нас
years now we have a War going on in our life,
годам сейчас у нас в жизни идёт Война
so it’s kind of intertwined, I
поэтому как бы ну переплетается я
’m trying to abstract myself. Let’s
стараюсь абстрагироваться Давайте
try another question, maybe it will work out
Попробуйте другой вопрос может получится
without war, I’m
без войны у меня
fine  what do you do in life?
как хорошо чем вы занимаетесь по жизни
That's where you work. Yes, I'm
Вот чем где работаете ко Да собираю
collecting, I'm collecting donations now for ZSU Yes, so that there are
собираю сейчас донаты на зсу Да чтобы
more gadgets, more Drones
больше всяких гаджетов больше Дронов
like beating up Russian occupiers at the
типа лупили российских оккупантов на
front
фронте
again, but that's ok Damn, let's give another
снова а капец капец Блин давайте другую
topic Who do you work let's give another
тему Кем Вы работаете давайте другую
topic again now it'll be about the war let's
тему снова сейчас будет о войне давайте
another topic is good Who did you study for? I
другую тему хорошо На кого вы учились Я
studied to be a programmer and this helps
учился на программиста и это помогает
me now earn more to
мне теперь зарабатывать больше чтобы
donate to the ZSU so that more breathing space for the
донатить на зсу чтобы больше по дыха
Russian occupiers who  they came to
российских оккупантов которые пришли на
ours again in the war I don’t know, I’m trying, I’m
наш опять на войне Не знаю я стараюсь я
trying, but somehow it comes out on its own
стараюсь но оно как-то оно само вылазит
Damn, let’s have another one, you’re just a topic,
Блин давайте другую вы просто тема
work is around money Let’s do
работа это вокруг денег Давайте другое
something else about life Well, where did you study
что-то о жизни Хорошо где вы учились
? Is it
Неужели
possible that it’s here again? I studied my first
если здесь опять прип Я учился первое
education  The Technological University of
образование технологический университет
Podillya is now called the Khmelnitsky
подолья сейчас называется Хмельницкий
National University of the Second; I
национальный университет второй э
received a legal education at the
юридическое образование получал в
University of Lida, management and rights.
лидском университете управление и права
Now the staff of these universities are
сейчас коллектив этих университетов
actively involved in helping the army
активно включился в помощь армии
collect drones. For example, my
собирает на дроны Вот например мой
native one, and the first university passed it on, I
родной да университет первый передал
also saw it even at the Department of Engineering, they
тоже видел даже на кафедре инженерных
are developing  some systems for
разрабатывают некоторые системы по
drones Yes, they let them into the army for
дронам Да пускают типа на армию их чтобы
more denazification
больше денацификация
[music]
[музыка]
so How old are you, if it’s not a secret,
так А сколько Вам лет если не секрет
well, no
ну без
reproaches. I’m 42 years old and for the last 10 years I’ve been
упрёков Мне 42 года и последних 10 лет Я
helping our army. Wait, I’ve been helping
помогаю нашей армии Подожди Я помогаю
our army, yes, I’ve been denating very intensively for the last 2 years
нашей армии да денаить последние 2 года
I help, we
очень интенсивно помогаю мы Warcraft
play Warcraft No, I don’t really play here, apparently
играем Нет не играю реально тут видимо
And where was I born? I was born in the city of
А где я родился Я родился в городе
Khmelnitsk Yes, in which there are a lot of
Хмельницке Да в котором очень много
bright people now helping the army so that
светлых людей сейчас помогает армии для
it is more effective  denazification
того чтобы она эффективнее денацификация
money yes In order for
деньги да Для того чтобы побольше и
us to grind it more and faster into minced meat
побыстрее мы их э на фарш
and it turns out you were born on the territory of the
м а вы получается родились на территории
USSR yes yes I was born on the territory of the
СССР да да я родился на на территории
Ukrainian Soviet Socialist
украинской Советской Социалистической
Republic which was part of the USSR
Республики которая входила в состав ССР
Yes and after it gained
Да и после того как она получила
independence the Russian Federation and  its
независимость Российская Федерация и её
reactionary forces could not come to terms with the
реакционные силы не смогли смириться с
fact that the Republics became independent and
тем что Республики стали независимы и
began to lead
стала вести
aggressive states, which led
захватнические государствам это привело
to the fact that in 2009 Russia attacked
к тому что в тым году Россия напала на
Ukraine  captured Crimea, Donetsk and Lugansk
Украину захватила Крым Донецк и Луганск
And now, instead of just
Да и сейчас мы вместо того чтобы просто
doing quiet things for ourselves, we are
себе заниматься спокойными делами мы
collecting for our army so that
собираем на нашу армию для того чтобы
the more denazification
чем больше денацификация
without this, this is a pretense, this is serious.
без этого вот наигранность вот серьёзно
Maybe you are running a Stream somewhere there. I don’t
Может вы где-то ведёте там Стрим Я не
know, but I’m just curious  what is
знаю но мне вот просто интересно какава
your personal opinion not not because of
вот какое личное ваше мнение не не из-за
what they say on television
то что у вас говорят на телевидении
just here is your personal opinion Why
просто вот ваше личное мнение Почему
Russia attacked Ukraine its goal we are my
Россия напала на Украину её цель мы мои
personal Yes my personal opinion because the
личное Да моё личное мнение потому что
majority of the population of Russia
большинство населения Российской
Federation uh and infected with an imperial
Федерации ээ и заражённой имперским
virus, it cannot produce anything normal,
вирусом оно ничего не может нормального
like for example America like
производить как например как Америка как
China is a Third World country and in
Китай есть страной Третьего мира и для
order to somehow compensate for its
того чтобы как-то компенсировать своё
internal This is uh let’s say
внутреннее Вот это э скажем
incapacity Yes, they want uh to
недееспособность Да они хотят ээ
take over neighboring countries to return sort of
захватить соседние страны вернуть вроде
like the Former Greatness there
как Былое Величие там
USSR Russian Empire that’s why
СССР Российскую империю поэтому
these appear Lenin created Ukraine
появляются вот эти Ленин создал Украину
Ukrainians never existed And the
украинцев никогда не существовало Да и
Russian Federation is waging
Российская Федерация ведёт
wars of conquest there in Georgia in
захватнические войны там в Грузии в
Ukraine in Moldova  and finally She
Украине в Молдове и наконец-то Она
received a serious rebuff on the territory of
получила серьёзный отпор на территории
Ukraine now with the help of the world
Украины сейчас с помощью ээ мировой
coalition, just as the Nazis were destroyed in thirty-
коалиции так же как нацистов в тридцать
nine forty-five. Also
девятом сорок пятом уничтожили Также
now the Nazis of the
сейчас происходит уничтожение нацистов
Russian Federation who invaded
Российской Федерации которые вторглись
the territory of Ukraine are being destroyed, after which Moldova will be
на территории Украины после этого будет
liberated, the issue with the Dniester will be closed
освобождена Молдова закроется вопрос с
and  will be liberated from the
пре днестром и будет освобождена сот
bicycle, look, I heard from you such a
вело смотрите я услышал от вас такой
term as Nazism. Do you understand what
термин как нацизм А вы ну понимаете что
Nazism is in general, yes Nazism was in the
такое вообще нацизм да нацизм был в
Third Reich and even now  found its
третьем рейхе Да и сейчас нашёл своё
reflection in the modern Russian
отображение в в современной Российской
Federation, which really is a
Федерации которая реально есть
Nazi state. Yes, we
нацистским государством Да мы очень
can very much see this in the Russian Federation.
можем видеть это в Российской Федерации
Hatred of other nations, the Nazis of the
Ненависть к другим нациям вот нацисты
Third Reich denied they did not give
третьего рейха отрицали не давали
subjectivity to the Jews. They said there
субъектности евреям Они там говорили
should be no Jews there, and so
никаких евреев не должно быть и так
on. Yes, Russia also carries out  with other
дальше Да Россия тоже проводит с другими
nations, including from Ukraine, these are
нациями в том числе из Украины вот эти
statements from the top leadership that
заявления высшего руководства что
Ukraine has never existed,
Украины никогда не существовала
Ukrainians do not exist, and so on, that
украинцев не существует и так дальше то
is, the Ukrainians there as a nation are denied
есть украинца там как нации отказывают в
subjectivity Yes, this is one of the signs of
субъектности Да это один из признаков
Nazism, further Russia is carrying out genocide of
нацизма дальше Россия проводит геноцид э
the population of Ukraine Yes, on ethnic
населения Украины Да по этническому
grounds, and we see that all the whole
признаку ээ и мы видим что все весь
nature of this war And the attitude,
характер этой войны Да и отношение в том
including towards the population of the Russian Federation of
числе и к населению Российской Федерации
non-Slavic origin Yes, we see
не Славянского происхождения Да мы видим
how they are cultivated in the Russian Federation
как в Российской Федерации
there are bad names of
культивируются там плохие названия
these different
разных этих
nations, jokes about different nations, and
Наций анекдоты про нации разные э
negative perceptions of people from
негативное восприятия людей из
Tajikistan, Uzbekistan, Kazakhstan, even
Таджикистана Узбекистана Казахстана даже
from the internal Russian territories there,
из внутренних российских территорий там
Buryatia Republic  Sakha Tatarstan
Бурятия Республика Саха Татарстан
Bashkartastan Dagestan Chechnya that's why
башкартастан Дагестан Чечня вот поэтому
Russia we saw in Russia all these
Россия мы видели в России эти все
Russian marches where they shouted Russia for
русские марши где кричали Россия для
Russians Moscow for Muscovites Russia is a
русских Москва для москвичей Россия
classic Nazi State and the
классическое нацистское Государство и
world coalition has united against it, an
против него объединилась мировая
interesting point
интересная точка
of view Another question is Well, not related to
зрения ещё Вопрос есть Ну не связанные с
the war, are you somehow connected
войной вы как-то связанные с войно
you ask questions from the war. So you lead everything
вопросы задаёте Так вы всё приводите
yourself to war, I asked you
сами к войне я вас задал
at all. If a person asks a question
вообще нельзя Если человек задаст вопрос
that cannot lead to war, no one
который нельзя привести к войне Никто не
can lead  to These are your questions that lead to war. Come on. Where do you study? Well, this immediately relates to the war. Let’s understand, let’s do it. Well, some topic that brought me these questions about the war and something connected with Take something abstract that you can’t come up with something abstract and not connected Look, now you can ask me a question where I’m studying, I can say that I’m studying to be a road builder and I’ll boil it down to the fact that in the future I will build a road to Kyiv But I can do this
сможет привести к Это ваши вопросы
not to say that I will build before I Vasya,
не сказать что я буду строить до я Васю
you will suggest some topic or
вы вы предложите какую-то тему или
question not related to the war.
вопрос не связанный с войной
Well, I already asked questions that in
Ну я уже задал вопросы которые никак в
no way concerned me, I’m sick of this
своём роде не касали меня задолбали эти
talk about the war, you come out and
уже разговоры о войне ты выходишь и
every Russian asks about something -  something about
каждый русский спрашивает о чём-то о
the war about politics or something connected with the
войне о политике или как-то связано с
war and politics You can just about
войной и с политикой Можете просто о
life has nothing to do with this
жизни не связано никак с вот этой
activity, look I don’t have
деятельность смотрите Я не имею никакого
any savvy in politics and
никакой подкованной в политики и в том
what’s going on there in the war for me it’s
что творится там на войне меня это
really well  I’m not interested This doesn’t
реально ну не интересует Меня это не
concern me directly because I
касается меня напрямую потому что я
don’t contribute to this in any way I don’t speak Ay
никак этому не способствуют я не мову Ай
My name is Nikita and I’m in no way
зовут Меня зовут Никита и я никак не
connected with what’s going on there ri understand I don’t
связан с тем что там ри понимаете Я не
want to talk about it Wait, do you
хочу об этом Говори Подождите а вы
know some hero of yours  name
знаете какого-то героя сво с именем
Nikita damn me again damn it real Yes so
Никита блин я снова блин реально Да так
let's Well, well, you
давайте Ну ну это
know, half everywhere it all somehow
понимаете полу всюду всю это как-то
seems yes And what's ugly is it So
кажется да А что некрасиво получа Вот
let's talk about beautiful ugly talk
давайте мы о красиво некрасиво поговорим
about beauty maybe there won't be a war here what's
о красоте может тут войны не будет что
ugly
некрасиво
is that Well what?  we are all arriving at
получается Ну то что мы всё прилетаем к
war. So it’s possible. Yes, well, what do you
войне Так возможно Да ну как бы а как вы
think, is bombed
считаете красивым ли есть разбомбленный
Mariupol beautiful? Is it beautiful or
Мариуполь Это красиво или
ugly? I can’t say my
некрасиво я не могу здесь сказать свою
point of view here, because I don’t have
точку зрения Потому что я не имею
any accurate information. You understand, everything is
никакой точной информации понимаете всё
subjective, what they say in your country, what they
субъективно что говорят у вас что
say in your country.
говорят у
us for 5 years for 2 years let's say a
нас за 5 лет за п ой за 2 года допустим
full-scale special operation you saw
полномасштабный спецоперации ты видел
photographs of Mariupol bombed
фотографии Мариуполя разбомбленный
you saw photographs of Kharkov
ты видел фотографии Харькова
shelled a friend from there you saw
обстрелянной друг оттуда ты видел
photographs of Bakhmut
фотографии бахмута
destroyed Well, you saw  fragments maybe he
уничтоженного Ну видел фрагменты может
saw everything that you still need What kind of
видел так всё та что тебе ещё надо Какая
Propaganda a Ukrainian city was destroyed
Пропаганда вот уничтожен украинский
before the Russian invasion he
город до российского вторжения он
lived normally after the Russian
нормально себе жил после российского
invasion it’s unclear what the
вторжения он у что те е
leadership from there decided that this was the way
т руководство оттуда решило что так надо
to do it you know what you think
поступить понимаете тея сю ты считаешь
Look you think it’s my opinion  It’s
Смотри ты считаешь моё мнение здесь
subjective here that people die in war It’s
субъективно что гибнут люди на войне Это
always there, there’s always been a war, it’s always
всегда есть всегда была война это всегда
I’m asking you so beautifully look
я тебя спрашиваю так красиво смотри
destroyed Bah, paint it or not I
уничтоженный Бах краси или нет Я вам
’m telling you directly that I think it’s war  -
говорю напрямую что я считаю что война -
this is bad and that everything that happens there
это плохо и что всё что там происходит
is very bad It’s ugly, war is
это очень плохо Это некрасиво война это
ugly  there are a
некрасиво Поня всё Поня то есть Путин
lot of people talking about war now
тоже сведу к войне сейчас очень много
when questions concern Putin Yes,
людей когда вопросы касаются Путина Да
when you need to say something like that, for some reason they remember
когда надо сказать что-то так вспоминают
a mop, I don’t know, some
почему-то швабру не знаю какой-то
military phenomenon like so interesting,
военный феномен типа такой интересный то
why don’t you say I wo
почему вы не скажете
n’t say  then why don’t you say that
не скажу то почему вы не скажете что
Putin did something ugly by attacking Ukraine, there
Путин сделал некрасиво напав на Украину
were reasons for this. So I can’t
для этого были причины Значит я не могу
judge him. What
судить его Какие
reasons do
причины
you know, but damn, again, I don’t have,
знаете а блин я опять же таки не имею
so to speak, the proper knowledge on this
так сказать должной подкованной данном
issue, I can’t talk about it with
вопросе не могу об этом говорить с
accurate
точной
information with great accuracy  but but
информацией с точностью большой но но
as they say that what in Ukraine What do you
как заявляют что что в Украине Что
know about the Cold War, well, if you
знаете холодную войну ну если историю
were interested in history Inter were interested in the fact that
интересовались Интере интересовались что
NATO,
в Турции располагались натовские
as far as I
насколько я
know, were located in Turkey as missile systems Yes, let’s name it
знаю как ракетные комплексы Да назовём
in general, I can’t say the same thing in
вообще я не могу сказать тоже самое на
Ukraine As
Украине Как
they say again, look, come on, so who
заявляют ещё раз смотри давай так кто
attacked? Well, who attacked whom, which country attacked which country,
напал Ну кто на кого напал какая страна
Ukraine was stolen from Russia, come
напала Укра полу Росси на Украину давай
on, when one country attacks another
так когда одна страна нападает на другую
country. Who is to
страну Кто
blame, well, you
виноват
can’t say so precisely here. Just
ну здесь нельзя так точно сказать Сразу
wait again, no, here it is.
погодите ещё раз нет здесь здесь так
it just won’t work, you understand if one side attacked the other. This is
одна строна напала на другую Это всего
just the one who took the first step, this
лишь тот кто сделал первый шаг у этого
has prerequisites, let’s look at it if
есть предпосылки давай так смотри в если
we look at international law,
мы посмотрим международное право
international law allows you to just
международное право разрешает просто так
attack a country or is there a definition
нападать на страну или есть определение
aggression yes savvy And not savvy, that
агрессии да подкован А не подкован то
is, you are where you need to be, you are savvy, you
есть ты где надо ты подкованный
start piling on where you need to, you are not
начинаешь наваливать где надо ты не
savvy, I’m where I was piling on you a minute,
подкован я вам где наваливал минуточку
you were piling on NATO missiles of some kind, the
ты наваливал натовские ракеты какие-то
first one didn’t attack, I told you right away
там первый на не напал м я Вам сразу
at the beginning of this whole dialogue, I don’t
сказал в начале всего этого диалога Я не
have  under the bones of this question Why if
имею под кости данном вопросе Зачем если
you don’t have Why what I heard
ты не имеешь Зачем том что я слышал
why did you look like that you heard if you don’t
зачем ты так смотри ты слышал если ты не
think it’s true somehow then why are
считаешь это правдой какой-то то зачем
you doing this  broadcasts
ты это транслирует
Well, I’m just bringing this to you because there
Ну я вам всего лишь довожу это по что
is such information well. You’ve
есть такая информация хорошо Ты слышал
heard the information, now try to
слышал информаци сейчас пытайтесь
get me to tell you directly
выудить о том чтобы я напрямую вам
who is to blame, but I won’t tell you that, you do
сказал кто виноват но я этого вам не
n’t know, I understand, yes, and you, for example,
скажу не не знаешь Поня да А ты например
have heard such versions. What, for example?
слы слышал такие версии Что например
Putin died like yes And instead of him
Путин умер типа да А вместо него
the double heard the version of course I hear
двойник слышал версию конечно слышу А
Why don’t you broadcast it you see you
почему ты её не транслирует ты видишь ты
broadcast the versions that you
транслирует версии которые тебе она
now she doesn’t need this version You
сейчас она сейчас не нужна эта версия
see That is, you broadcast
Вот видишь То есть ты транслирует
some versions Yes which you hear that  is it
какие-то версии Да которые слышишь что
convenient for you? You are now trying to say something
удобно Вы сейчас пытаетесь сказать то
that you are trying to bring me to the point where
что чтобы пытаетесь меня довести до того
I tell you what you need, that
чтобы я вам сказал то что вам нужно что
someone is to blame, it is necessary, yes, because
кто-то виноват нужно да да потому что
someone is to blame, someone is to blame. Well,
кто-то виноват кто-то же виноват Ну
look, when one country attacks
смотри когда одна страна нападает на
another, why?  you are looking for the culprit, but
другую зачем вы ищете виновного а потому
because to
что чтобы
figure it out Yes, I want to understand, maybe My
разобраться Да я хочу понять может Моя
country is to blame and then we need to
страна виновата и тогда нам нужно
tell Zelensky, damn Zelensky, we are
сказать зеленскому блин Зеленский мы
to blame Let’s withdraw the troops,
виноваты Давай отведём войска да
maybe so, let’s figure it out
может так давайте вот мы разберёмся
For example, you and I, it doesn’t work like that, what are we doing
Например я и вы это так не работает мы
now  Look, I’m not interested in
что сейчас смотри я не интересуюсь
politics and you’re not interested. Let’s
политикой и вы не интересуетесь Давайте
take an interest in politics now and
Поинтересуйся сейчас политикой и
figure out who’s to blame. Well, I think, like
разберёмся кто же виноват Ну я думаю как
in mine, I think that in such a short
в моём думаю что за такой короткий
conversation We’ll understand at least
разговор Мы я разберусь по крайней мере
politics, as I see it, you Horseshoe Although
в политике я так смотрю вы Подкова Хотя
Well, more than me, much more  what am I talking about
Ну больше чем я намного больше чем я про
Well, I’m just already today I
Ну я просто за сегодня уже Я сегодня
downloaded chat roulette today I’ve already talked to 10 people
скачал чат рулетку Я уже 10 человек
I’m already savvy in
пообщался Я уже подковал подкованный в
this Yes, I’m already in our politics I think, well,
этом Да я уже в политике наша я думаю ну
we are now  Maybe we’re not so damned
и мы сейчас можем мы же не такие блин
there that in the Kremlin and in the Verkhovna Rada they
там что в Кремле и в Верховной Раде
sit smarter than us. We’ll also figure it out,
сидят умнее нас Мы ж тоже ж разберёмся
but in my opinion, the look is like that,
вот в мо на мой хлопки взгляд такой да
since Russia attacked Ukraine, it means that
что раз Россия напала на Украину Значит
she is to
она и
blame for what she is to blame. Let’s say that she
виновата в чём виновата Давайте Так в
attacked  to a foreign
том что напала на чужую
country Well, in the sense of, wait a minute, to be
страну Ну в смысле не погодите быть
guilty for something for which she for an
виновным за что-то за что она за
attack means for aggression
нападение значит за агрессию на на по
towards another
отношению к другой
country And on this side there was no
стране А с этой стороны не было никакой
aggression, you want to say  we didn’t
агрессии вы хотите сказать мы не
attack, you can say that Ukraine
нападали можете сказать чтобы Украина
crossed the border there and somewhere there attacked
там перешла границу и где-то там напала
Russia for good I just have a
на Россию для хорошо У меня просто к вам
question for you to figure out what
вопрос такой мне чтобы разобраться что
happened with the Donbass that was shelled
тогда с донбассом который обстреливали
Donbass is Ukraine Donbass is
Донбасс - это Украина Донбасс - это
Ukraine why was it shelled then
Украина почему его тогда обстреливали
so wait  Well, look at it, let me
так подожди Ну смотри его давай так
explain it to Ukraine. Yes, I explain. Look,
Украины ещё объясняю Да объясняю Смотри
Donbass is not Donbass Donbass is
вот Донбасс не Донбасс Донбасс - это
Ukraine Crimea is Ukraine  What difference does it make to
Украина Крым - это Украина какая разница
you what is being done even if there
вам что делается даже если тут
was shelling here, for example, if in Iran
обстреливали например вот если в Иране
Yes, uh, they are shelling something there, but you are
Да ээ что-то там обстреливают да Вы же
not attacking
не нападает на
Iran in China, for example, something is
Иран в Китае например что-то там
being done there. You are not attacking China, yes,
делается Вы же не нападает на Китай да
these are internal matters, even if we
это дела внутренне даже если бы мы
fired Yes, why did you attack us I
обстреливали Да почему вы напали на нас
can’t answer this is an interesting question,
уже не могу отве вот интересный вопрос
I also don’t have the proper information yes
тоже я не владею должной информацией да
What do you think when Hitler
Как вы считаете когда Гитлер в тридцать
and the Soviet Union
девятом году вместе с советским союзом
attacked Poland in 1939, Poland was to blame
напали на Польшу виновата была Польша
or Hitler and the Soviet
или Гитлер и Советский
Union Hitler rather Although Why not
Союз Гитлер скорее Хотя А почему не
Poland
Польша А
Why wait now we need to remember
почему сейчас погодить надо припомнить
history Okay, let’s make it simpler forty-one
историю Хорошо давайте проще сорок
Hitler attacked the Soviet
первый год Гитлер напал на Советский
Union Who is
Союз Кто
to blame, you know, Hitler had a different
виноват понимаете у Гитлера была иная
goal, no, well, who is to blame Who’s to blame
цель не ну кто виноват Кто виноват
Let’s Who’s to blame Hitler attacked  USSR
Давайте Кто виноват Гитлер напал на СССР
who is
кто
to blame for Yes, in this situation, Hitler
виноват в Да в данной ситуации Гитлер
is to blame, but there is an explanation why
виноват но тут Есть объяснение почему
Why Because I have
Почему Потому что я владею
more explain why he is to blame yes
больше обясните почему он виноват да
Explain, see
Объясните смотрите
Hitler Well, let’s put it this way, he led an
Гитлер Ну скажем так
aggressive policy
сформулировать вёл захват скую политику
and Russia is pursuing an
и Россия ведёт
aggressive policy more reasons than
захватнических больше причины нежели
capture this kuso of it Well, well, there is an
захватить вот такой вот кусо её Ну ну
aggressive policy, yes,
захватническая политика есть есть да
annexing territories, everything is clear
присоединяя территории есть всё чётко
further Why Hitler was here There
дальше Почему Гитлер был здесь Здесь
is something more than just a seizure
есть что-то больше чем просто захват
Maybe maybe let's also Why was there
Может может давайте вот ещ Почему ги был
wine, he led
вино он вёл
like this back and forth there  - it’s hard to
вот так вот туда-сюда туда-сюда неже
say here Well, well, well, somehow
сказать Ну хорошо Ну ты как-то
your brain definitely determine that Hitler is
однозначно твой мозг Определи что Гитлер
to blame, so I’m saying. By what criteria is
виноват вот я говорю По каким критериям
he to blame? How do you determine that he is
он виноват как ты определишь что он
to blame? I don’t understand you, wait a little,
виноват я не понимаю вас немножко
what do you mean by
погодите что вы подразумеваете под
in a word, you’re guilty Well, look,
словом виноват вот ты Ну смотри Каждый
everyone understands, look, you can be
каждый понимает смотрите можно быть
guilty for the death of people, you can be
виноватым за за смерть людей може быть
guilty
виноват
for the verb guilty Yes, and it doesn’t
за глагол виноватый Да и вина так она не
require guilt, all the ponies What is guilty,
требует все пони Что такое виноват да
yes Now you’re starting such a verbal
Вот Вы сейчас начинаете такую словесную
balancing act, it’s just that you’re guilty for
эквилибри вот просто ги виноват что
attacking  SSR or not
напал на ССР или не
I’m to blame once again, I then
виноват я ещё раз я вас тогда уже
stop
перестаю
understanding you Why can he be to blame for
понимать За что может он виноват за
the loss to Germany,
проигрыш Германии во
maybe he can be to blame for the attack
может можно быть виноватым за нападение
I don’t understand this then Let’s
Я не понимаю вот этого тогда уже Давайте
when when someone comes up to you on the street
когда когда вам на улице кто-то подойдёт
and hits you  in the nose he is to blame or
и ударит в нос он виноват или
he is to blame for the fact that I, let’s say, suffered
он виноват за то что я допустим понёс
damage. This is why he will be
ущерб Вот за это он будет
to blame when Hitler attacked the Soviet
виноват когда Гитлер напал на Советский
Union Hitler was to blame that the Soviet
Союз Гитлер был виноват что Советский
Union suffered damage or the Soviet Union was
Союз понёс ущерб или Советский Союз был
to blame that Hitler suffered damage Hitler
виноват что Гитлер понёс ущерб Гитлер
will be to blame in this context will be
будет виноват в таком контексте будет
Hitler understood that it was his fault, yes When Russia
виноват Гитлер так понял да Когда Россия
attacked Ukraine Who is
напала на Украину Кто
to blame Maybe Ukraine is to blame that She
виноват Может и Украина виновата что Она
led
вела
dude the fact that you have an inner core is
чувак то что у тебя внутренний стержень
not a core, it’s Putin’s mop
- это не стержень это Путинская швабра у
under your tonsils
тебя стоит под гланды
Let's subscribe to my Telegram directly at once
Давай подпишись на мий Telegram прямо
axis vin and popk
зараз ось вин а попк
more and more respectfully YouTube keeping us busy
це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня нас
through skarg or in new ban and even more
через скарг ор в ньй бан и дуже багато
richly video I don’t show people immediately I don’t show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams For this purpose,
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
we need Mali operational link to write
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
directly at once  bye there in telegram okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телеграми окм
video sche tezh va and korisna information and
видео ще теж ва и корисна информация и
We will tell you about the postiyny
мы пон з вами трима постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
in order to show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine write
YouTube Слава Украине пиши